Rafael Zoldan

(054) 2256204 zoldan.rafael@gmail.com

Profiles:





Rafazoldan.com

Languages:

Spanish (mother tongue) English (fluent) Hebrew (fluent)

Education:

2019

Netcraft Academy: Full Stack Development course

2011 - 2014

The COLLMAN: Master in Business Administration

2001 - 2006 Universidad San Francisco de Quito:BA - Advertising & Communications Minor in photography

Summary

Motivated and resourceful Full Stack Developer with three years' experience in software development and one year of formal training. Adept at managing and supervising teams, while also a responsible and hard-working team player. Performance-driven with strong attention to detail. Thrilled by new challenges.

Skills

HTML 5, CSS 3, Sass Javascript, ES6 Node.js, MongoDB, Python React Webpack Git

Experience:

黨

12/2019 - Present



Developing the front-end for a startup with a social impact mission using: React, ES6, Firebase, git, agile methodology.

04/2018 - 10/2019

VP Digital Operations and Marketing Recovery Health (Strokemark.com)

Setup, and management of all digital systems and processes including Wordpress, Hubspot, Twilio, Gsuite, Tagmanager, Datastudio, Zendesk, Adwords, Facebook, Twitter, Mailchimp.

Team management leading our client service representatives and third party software developers.



10/2010 - 12/2017

Operations Director and Technical Support Albert Technologies LTD

In charge of customer Technical Support and API integration.

In charge of Innovation Projects including research, design, proof of concept, budget management, lead development with the R&D team.

 Manage third party systems (Adwords, Facebook, CRM, Dashboard, ad servers, video players, tracking systems, reporting tools) serving as technical support.

 Trained all new employees on RTB, tracking, and platforms usage